Cole Waggoner

Tampa, FL ♦ waggcj02@gmail.com ♦ (850) 481-5468 ♦ http://www.linkedin.com/in/colejwaggoner

Summary

As a Statistics major at the University of South Florida (USF), and from experience in full stack development, I have gained technical knowledge of many coding languages along with using that knowledge to solve complex problems. I am a passionate team member who is always striving to improve existing methods to increase value and optimization. As an outgoing worker, I constantly seek constructive criticism to enhance my skills, and I value feedback from my colleagues.

In addition, I possess unique skills that have been developed through lifelong pursuits, including personal teaching, problem-solving, project design and completion, and I excel most in being able to learn/apply new skills quickly. These skills make me highly creative and adaptable, with a talent for designing and completing projects with exceptional attention to detail.

Overall, my combination of technical expertise, passion for process optimization, and unique skills make me a valuable asset to any team.

Education

Bachelor of Arts in Statistics, University of South Florida, Tampa, FL Expected May 2024

Full Stack Web Development Certificate, University of Central Florida, Orlando, FL

Professional Experience

Hibbett Sports, Panama City, FL

March 2021 – December 2022

Manager

- Assisted in making the store the #1 earning location in the district; which includes most of Florida, Georgia,
 and Alabama
- Saw a 50% increase in yearly sales after being hired
- Assists customers and manages store employees.
- Partook in hiring processes and interviews.
- Train new hires in sales and customer service.
- Gained essential problem solving skills as it relates to difficult customers and meeting company policies.
- Grew social media following through local events and community outreach.
- Saw significant store sales gains through customer interaction and focus on promoting top selling items

NIKE, Panama City Beach, FL

July 2020 - February 2021

Athlete

- Learned and retained knowledge of all relevant products created by Nike past and present.
- Assisted customers and inventory monitoring.
- Trained new hires in sales, customer service, and company/product information.
- Took on projects that increased productivity on surveys and had substantial increases in positive results.

Gulf Coast Regional Medical Center, Panama City, FL

April 2018 - August 2019

Patient Transporter

- Required to gather patients for necessary exams (CT scans, X-Rays, MRI's)
- Checked patients exemptions for certain exams
- Developed strong interpersonal skills while assisting patients of all ages.
- Learned detailed knowledge of medical technology and its appropriate uses.

Veterinary Medical Center, Tampa, FL

July 2023 - Present

Veterinary Assistant

- Helped with taking care of various animals while in our care
- Kept the clinic clean and organized
- Interacted with clients to ensure a positive experience
- Entered shipments and ensured an organized stockroom

Vinik Sports Group, Tampa, FL

July 2023 - Present

Ticket Sales

- Assisted customers with ticket troubleshooting and purchasing
- Aided customers in finding their seats
- Ensured tickets were valid and connected to the correct customer

Additional Coursework & Skills

Software Experience: R, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, MongoDB, React, SQL, Tableau, API Implementation, NodeJS, GitHub, Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Adobe Premiere, Photoshop, After Effects

Volunteer Experience

Volunteer, Helping Hands, Panama City, FL

- Organized large cleanup operations for hurricane recovery
- Aided in daily recovery such as removing trees from rooftops

Honors and Awards

- Eagle Scout
- Top 10% in graduating class, Mosley High School

Additional Links

• GitHub: https://github.com/ColeWaggoner

• LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/cole-waggoner-64aaa3199/

• Portfolio: https://colewaggoner.github.io/02-Portfolio/